{
    "id": "8d015bbf6cfe45419445de7e83d12dee",
    "title": "Simple Present Tense Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "....................... you know his name?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Do",
                "Does",
                "Has"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "602f1fdb49424984aba360c97cddcc8e"
        },
        {
            "question": "We ..................... . strangers.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do not trust",
                "does not trust",
                "have not trust"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "70b1d7a5a3b74434ae82bd1339f9c79a"
        },
        {
            "question": "Arun .....................… with his left hand.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "write",
                "writes",
                "writing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "a79a8b6087e24f5cac2bdc7603c13485"
        },
        {
            "question": "Salim ..................... for the national hockey team.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "play",
                "plays",
                "playing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "ca629151215b4f53a3ce0b362ac37b2d"
        },
        {
            "question": "My parents ....................... me to get good grades.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "want",
                "wants",
                "wanting"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "374d66cab5ac4e699f6aedf742a157b6"
        },
        {
            "question": "Where ...................... you live?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "does",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d30d6b4526c44c49925909cf428e45f8"
        },
        {
            "question": "What ………………. he do?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "do",
                "does",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "67919a68249d4c098735d884c8af4257"
        },
        {
            "question": "Rahul ………………….. not have a job.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "does",
                "do",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "87a4e2b4dc5648ef858d9b65ce544716"
        },
        {
            "question": "Shiva ..................... . an apartment in the city.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "own",
                "owns",
                "owning"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d456a2d9446544b1adad7d8f4e6cae4b"
        },
        {
            "question": "Gauri ....................... lovely long hair.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "has",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "3eee4d46ec084a51b7aa25019d0978dd"
        }
    ]
}